detector-invisible.com 2016-10-20

# Privacy Policy | Detector-Invisible.com

**Detector-Invisible.com Privacy Policy**

This site is not related in any way with Yahoo.com or any other site.

Your privacy is of extreme importance to us. This **[privacy policy](http://www.detector-invisible.com/privacy-policy.php "privacy policy")** outlines what personal information is collected and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other web servers, **[Detector-Invisible.com](http://www.detector-invisible.com/ "Detector Invisible")** uses log files. The information inside them include, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Advertising partners and other third parties may use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. Detector-Invisible.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Controlling Your Privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Detector-Invisible.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Detector-Invisible.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - **<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>**
